<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NutriAll</string>
    <string name="wtloss">

        <b>1. Add, Don\'t Subtract</b> \n\n
        Forget diet denial: Try adding foods to your diet instead of subtracting them.
        Add in healthy goodies you really love, like deep-red cherries, juicy grapes,
        or crunchy snow peas. Slip those favorite fruits into your bag lunch and breakfast
        cereal; add the veggies into soups, stews, and sauces.\n\n

        <b>2. Lighten the Foods You Already Love</b> \n\n
        One of the easiest ways to cut back without feeling denied is to switch to lower-calorie
        versions of the foods you crave. A pizza tastes just as good with reduced-fat cheese, and
        when you garnish low-fat ice cream with your favorite toppers, who notices those missing calories?\n\n

        <b>3. Because Hydration Helps -- Really!</b> \n\n
        Down some water before a meal and you won\'t feel so famished, says David Anthony, an information
        technology consultant from Atlanta. "Drinking a glass of water before a meal helps me watch what
        I eat. … I don\'t just hog everything, since I\'m not so hungry."\n\n

        <b>4. Do not overtake the stimulants</b>\n\n
        Avoid frequent drinking of tea and coffee in a day. Also stop the consumption of bed tea or bed coffee.
        Because the use of caffeine is harmful when you take it on an empty stomach. It raises the stress level
        which is a reason for the increase of hunger. So, you can understand that caffeine is a reason for obesity indirectly.\n\n

        <b>5. Drink Plenty of water</b>\n\n
        Water is a zero calorie drink with low sodium. It helps flush out the toxic substances build-up inside the body.
        Frequent water consumption increases the rate of metabolism.\n

        You can drink the solution of lemon, honey, and water in the early morning. Or you can have the coconut water alone.
        This helps to keep your body hydrated and maintain the electrolyte balance in the body.\n\n

        <b>6. Do not skip breakfast</b>\n\n
        Rules for Obesity
        Breakfast is the most important meal of the day. If you skip breakfast, you will be less active for the whole day
        . The people who skip breakfast are more forgetful than the people who eat breakfast. Skipping breakfast is a 21%
        reason for type II diabetes. So, you should eat something like a cup of yogurt or a cup of porridge. Also, you can
        eat cucumber slices or drink carrot juice on an empty stomach.\n\n

        <b>7. Do not keep your stomach hungry</b>\n\n
        People try to avoid eating with a thought of fasting helps to reduce the weight. But, keeping your stomach hungry
        leads to some side effects. They are headaches, dizziness, lightheadedness, fatigue, low blood pressure and abnormal
        heart rhythms. So, eat well to fulfill your nutritional needs and avoid the side effects.\n\n

        <b>8. Have an early last meal</b>\n\n
        Eating in the initial hours of the night is one of the excellent weight loss treatments. You will have some health
        benefits of early dinners. They are weight control, peaceful sleep, healthier heart, more time for digestion, etc.

        You can also prevent the burning sensation that occurs when you eat heavily in the nights. And also you will start the
        day with more energy. So, make a habit of dinners 3 hours before the sleep.\n\n

        <b>9. Control the calorie intake!</b>\n\n
        Reduce Calorie Intake\n
        Reduce Calorie Intake\n
        To have a fit and healthy body, you should keep an eye on the calorie food intake. High calories in your food lead to
        many health issues. They are diabetes, heart attack, cognitive impairment, osteoarthritis, etc. So try to avoid the
        high calorie food if you want to lose weight fast.

    </string>
    <string name="avita">

    Important for eyesight,skin health, the immune system, body and bone growth, and development of cells.\n
    Vitamin A can be found in foods derived from animals such as liver and fish oil, milk, and eggs. In plants vitamin A exists as
    Beta-Carotene in dark green leafy and orange vegetables.\n\n

    <b>Required intake</b>\n
    Men: 900 mg/day\n
    Women: 700 mg/day

    </string>

    <string name="bvita">

        The job of Vitamin B is to help the metabolize carbohydrates, fats, and amino acids in the body turning them into fuel for the
        body to use as energy. There are 8 different B vitamins. Thiamin, Riboflavin, Niacin, Folate, B6 and B12, Biotin, and Panthothenic
        acid. All are important in energy metabolism.\n
        These vitamins can be found in liver, bananas, spinach, potatoes and chicken breast. \n\n

    <b>Required intake</b>\n
    Men: 15 mg/day\n
    Women: 12 mg/day

    </string>

    <string name="cvita">

        This Vitamin is important in the development of collagen which is the connective tissue such as bones, skin and tendons. It is
        also an antioxidant which protect the cells from oxidizing themselves which prevent disease. \n
        Lots of fruits like oranges, grapefruit and vegetables such as peppers and broccoli are important sources of vitamin C.\n\n

    <b>Required intake</b>\n
    Men: 90 mg/day\n
    Women: 75 mg/day

    </string>

    <string name="dvita">

        This is a unique vitamin in that with the help of the sun the body can synthesize all it needs. But many people do not get enough sun
        exposure so they must get vitamin D through food. The main job of vitamin D is to help regulate calcium in the body which is essential
        for bone, muscle, tissue. nerve and gland renewal.\n
        Vitamin D can be found in foods such as fish, milk, fortified cereals.\n\n

    <b>Required intake</b>\n
        Adults: 15 mg/day

    </string>

    <string name="evita">

        Vitamin e is an essential as an antioxidant that fights off free radicals which can cause premature aging, cancer, heart disease, and more.\n
        It is found mostly in fresh, raw vegetable oil sources. It is important that they are minimally processed in order to have the best
        sources. \n\n


    <b>Required intake</b>\n
        Adults: 15 mg/day
    </string>


    <string name="kvita">

        This is the vitamin that is essential in blood clotting. Too much vitamin K can cause blood clots in the heart, whee too little
        will cause a person to bleed to quickly, Vitamin K is also important in building bone protein.\n
        Dark green leafy vegetables, broccoli, brussels sprouts, and cabbages are good sources of Vitamin K, \n\n

    <b>Required intake</b>\n
    Men: 120 mg/day\n
    Women: 90 mg/day

    </string>


</resources>
